[{"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! wow, it is true what they say, pregnant bellies look like a drum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  ha-ha.  no, it\u0092s just i\u0092m so pregnant that i\u0097my guitar doesn\u0092t fit anymore. so i thought \u0091til i\u0092m not, i\u0092m just gonna play all my songs on this drum. it sounds really cool!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " listen. listen.  smelly cat, smelly cat, what are they feeding you?", "answer": " wow, pheebs! that sounds great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i know! i know, and i\u0092ve only been playing for like an hour!", "answer": "  phoebe! phoebe! hi! hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hey! what are you doing here?", "answer": " umm, actually, i came down to ask you a big favour.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh, well, don\u0092t tell me you want to keep more of your stuff in my uterus.", "answer": "  no. no. no.  okay, now, see, i wanna name the girl baby leslie, and frank wants to name one of the boy babies frank jr. jr.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " wouldn\u0092t that be frank the iii?", "answer": " don\u0092t get me started.  anyway, umm, since there are three babies and umm, we both got to put our names in, we would be truly honoured if you named the other boy baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " wow! that\u0092s so great! oh! oh! cougar.", "answer": " you think about it.  opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " i left a bra drying on the shower rod, you don\u0092t think your son will think it\u0092s yours and be horribly traumatised?", "answer": " hey, if mommy can have a wife, daddy can have a bra.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": "  ohh, it\u0092s time to go.", "answer": " oh, no-no-no, see, that-that clock\u0092s a little fast, uh, we have 17 minutes. huh, what can we do in 17 minutes? twice?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hey, uh, you can ignore that.", "answer": " that\u0092s carol with your son!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " uhh, believe me when he\u0092s older, he\u0092ll understand.", "answer": "  ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i\u0092ll be right there.   hello!  hello!  hey. uhh, emily, this is carol and susan.", "answer": " hey, it\u0092s so nice to finally meet you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " me too!", "answer": " ohh, y\u0092know, susan\u0092s gonna be shooting a commercial in london next week.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh yeah, i\u0092m so excited, i\u0092ve never been there.", "answer": " oh, well, i\u0092ll show you around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " that would be great! also, uh, i was hoping to catch a show so if you can make any suggestions\u009a", "answer": " oh, there\u0092s tonnes of terrific stuff\u0097i\u0092ll go with you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " look at you two, bonding, making us late for the airport so\u009a", "answer": " are you all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, he\u0092s fine. he\u0092s fine. it\u0092s just that us getting along is difficult for him, because he doesn\u0092t like me.", "answer": " oh come on! that\u0092s-that\u0092s\u009a true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey! do we have a baby name yet?", "answer": " ugh! no! this is so hard! i went through this whole book  and found nothing! i want a name that\u0092s really like, y\u0092know strong and confident, y\u0092know? like-like exxon.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, it certainly worked for that valdez kid.", "answer": " ooh-ooh, pheebs, you want a strong name? how about, the hulk?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " no, i\u0092m-i\u0092m not sure about hulk, but i like the idea of a name starting with \"the.\"", "answer": " oh, want a good name, go with joey. joey\u0092s your pal. joey\u0092s your buddy. \"where is everybody?\" \"well, they\u0092re hanging out with joey.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " hey, y\u0092know what, if you\u0092re gonna do that, if you\u0092re gonna name him joey, you should name him chandler.  oh, come on! chandler\u0092s funny, sophisticated, and he\u0092s very loveable, once you get to know him.", "answer": " oh well, hey, joey\u0092s loveable too! but the thing about joey is, if you need him, he\u0092ll be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well, chandler will be there for you too. i mean, well, he might be a little late, but-but, he\u0092ll be there. and he\u0092ll bring you some cold soda, if want you need him for is that you\u0092re really hot.", "answer": " what do ya say? what do ya say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " well, i, i like the idea of naming him after someone i love, and joey and chandler are great names.  but, all right, i don\u0092t\u0097maybe i\u0092ll just name him the hulk.", "answer": " i knew i shouldn\u0092t have mentioned it! that\u0092s what i wanted to name my kid!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " y\u0092know what? it really creeps me out choosing other people\u0092s sex clothes.", "answer": " sorry. i\u0092m so exited! i\u0092ve been waiting for this for months! i got my hair coloured! i got new sheets! i\u0092m making him a very fancy meal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " um-hmm.", "answer": " what am i making him by the way?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " well, you\u0092re making him a frieze salad with goat cheese and pine nuts, wild nuts, wild rice, roast asparagus, and salmon au croup.", "answer": " i thought i was making him filet mignon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " yeah, you were, but you decided to make salmon because you had some left over at the restaurant. and then you realised if you  bitched about it, then you  would stop cooking, and you  would have to make your famous baked potato and diet coke.", "answer": " wow, i really get crabby when i cook.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so uh, emily called last night\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " and now you\u0092re giving me the message!", "answer": " turns out them emily is just crazy about susan. yeah, they\u0092re going to the theatre together! they\u0092re going to dinner! they\u0092re going horseback riding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " god, susan is so fun!", "answer": " look, this is just a little too familiar, okay? for like, for like six months before carol and i spilt up, all i heard was: \"my friend susan is so smart. my friend susan is so funny. my friend susan is so great.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " you actually think that something can happen between emily and susan?", "answer": " hey, they\u0092re going to the gym together! two women! stretching! y\u0092know they-they take a steam together! things get a little playful\u0097didn\u0092t you see personal best?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " no, but i\u0092m gonna!", "answer": " hi! hi! you\u0092re crazy! okay? this is emily. emily is straight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " how do you know? i mean we thought carol was straight before i married her!", "answer": " yeah, i definitely. i don\u0092t like the name ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " what a weird way to kick me when i\u0092m down.", "answer": " no! no! i-i meant for the baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh. what\u0092s wrong with ross?", "answer": " well, it\u0092s just y\u0092know that something like this would never to like the hulk, y\u0092know\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " so, i decided i\u0092m definitely going to go with either joey or chandler.", "answer": " oh! oh-oh, you gotta pick joey! i mean, name one famous person named chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " raymond chandler.", "answer": " someone you didn\u0092t make up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " okay, there are no famous joey\u0092s. except for, huh, joey buttafucco.", "answer": " yeah, that guy really hurt us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well, how about a compromise then, okay? what if it\u0092s like y\u0092know, chanoey?", "answer": " okay, look, joey! come on, think about it, first of all, he\u0092ll never be president. there\u0092s never gonna be a president joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " all right look man, i didn\u0092t want to bring this up, but chandler, is the stupidest name i ever heard in my life! it\u0092s not even a name; it\u0092s barely even a word. okay? it\u0092s kinda like chandelier, but it\u0092s not! all right? it\u0092s a stupid, stupid non-name!", "answer": " wow, you\u0092re, you\u0092re right. i have a horrible, horrible name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " so i guess it\u0092s joey then!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " this is so nice. thank you for doing this.", "answer": " ohh, please! cooking soothes me.  ahh. so, dig in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " great! oh, it all looks sooo good!", "answer": "  hmmm!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh i know, my god, this is so\u0097this rice is so\u0097i am so good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " behind you?", "answer": "  oh, yeah, i\u0092m sorry. they used to live here; sometimes they migrate back over.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  is there ah, is there some way they can not be here. it\u0092s just ah, farm birds really kinda freak me out!", "answer": " yeah, sure, okay. okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " all gone! so, farm birds, huh?", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s-it\u0092s my only weird thing, i swear. and i-i-i would\u0092ve told you about it, but i didn\u0092t know they would be here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " so, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " nothing i uh, it\u0092s just that i know that they\u0092re still out there.", "answer": " but, they\u0092re across the hall! i mean that\u0092s two doors away, it would take them a long time to peck their way back over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay, that\u0092s-that\u0092s not funny. uhh.", "answer": " okay, y\u0092know, would you feel better if we went someplace else? i mean we could pack all this stuff up and y\u0092know go to your apartment.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " oh, they\u0092re working on this week, it\u0092s a total mess. but uh, i\u0092m staying at my parents\u0092 house, we could go there.", "answer": " your parents\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah, they\u0092re out of town.", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah-yeah, it\u0092s this huge place, and-and it\u0092s got this gorgeous view of the park, and very, very romantic. what do you say?", "answer": " yeah that works.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! how\u0092s ben?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hey, ben! hey!", "answer": " so umm, any word from susan?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ooh, yeah! she said she\u0092s having sooo much fun with emily.", "answer": " uh-huh. uh-huh. uh, by the by, did it uh, did it ever occur to you that, i don\u0092t know, maybe they might be having a little too much fun?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what\u0092s too much fun?", "answer": " y\u0092know, the kind of fun, you and susan had when we were married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh my god, you are so paranoid!", "answer": " am i?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " am i?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " i can\u0092t speak for emily, but susan is in a loving, committed relationship.", "answer": " uh-huh, carol, so were we. all right, just-just imagine for a moment, susan meets someone and-and they really hit it off. y\u0092know? say-say they\u0092re coming back from the theatre, and they-they stop at a pub for a couple of drinks, they\u0092re laughing, y\u0092know, someone innocently touches someone else\u009a there\u0092s electricity, it\u0092s new. it\u0092s exciting. are you telling me there isn\u0092t even the slightest possibility of something happening?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " maybe.", "answer": " oh my god!! i didn\u0092t really believe it until you just said it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " \u009aand even though none of the other kids believed me, i swear to god, that duck pushed me!", "answer": " wow! this place is fabulous!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, let me show you around. this is the uh, downstairs living room.", "answer": " whoa-whoa, there\u0092s two living rooms? god, growing up here, this place must\u0092ve been a real babe magnet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah, well, it would\u0092ve been, but uh, my parents just moved here.", "answer": " ohh, you should know, this place is a real babe magnet. wanna make out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hey, here\u0092s an idea. why don\u0092t uh, i put the food in the fridge and we can eat it later?", "answer": " that sounds like a plan. umm, is there a place i can go freshen up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh yeah, yeah uh, it\u0092s down the hall and uh, second door to your left.", "answer": " ah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, hi, darling!", "answer": " mom, dad, what are you guys doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, well we cut the trip short.", "answer": " france sucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " umm, this may be a little weird, but i-i-i got a date here.", "answer": " oh, say no more!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " we\u0092ll just grab some food and take it with us right upstairs, and we\u0092ll be right out of you hair.", "answer": " oh, that-that would be great. so you didn\u0092t even get to italy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " hi you!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " uhh, rachel, my parents\u009a", "answer": " ohh! it\u0092s so nice to meet you.  hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hello. well, joshua, that $500 was for groceries.", "answer": " what? this-this, no, oh no, no-no-no, this is not\u0097that\u0092s-that\u0092s not what it is. see, see, okay, i work in fashion, see and-and, this is a real dress actually. it\u0092s-it\u0092s, they\u0092re-they\u0092re wearing it in milan, so part of my job is too wear the clothes, and then i see how people respond, and then i report back to my superiors at bloomingdale\u0092s, so\u009a and obviously in uh, in-in this case,  i am going to report back, \"usa not ready.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " maybe in l.a?", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " there you go.", "answer": " so, have you kids eaten yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, we were going to do that after\u0097i mean umm, next.", "answer": " well, we\u0092re starving, why don\u0092t we all go get something to eat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh, yeah, well\u009a yeah, no use wasting this baby, just lyin\u0092 around the house.", "answer": " so\u009a we go eat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " yes.", "answer": " you\u0092ll wear that. we\u0092ll be eating, and of course, you\u0092ll be wearing that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " dude, i am sorry about what i said!", "answer": " no, no, you\u0092re right, it is a ridiculous name!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it\u0092s not that bad.", "answer": " yes it is! from now on, i have no first name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " so, you\u0092re just bing?", "answer": " i have no name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " all right, so, what are we supposed to call you?", "answer": " okay uh, for now, temporarily, you can call me, clint.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no way are you cool enough to pull of clint.", "answer": " okay, so what name am i cool enough to pull off?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " umm, gene.", "answer": " it\u0092s clint. it\u0092s clint!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " see you later, gene.", "answer": " bye, gene.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " it\u0092s clint! clint!", "answer": " what\u0092s up with gene?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " so, you wore your nightie to dinner?", "answer": " oh, yeah. and uh, the best part though, when the uh, waiter spilled water down my back, i jumped up, and my boob popped out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh, no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  so, i just picked up a message from emily, she and susan are going to a poetry reading together!", "answer": " so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " so! poetry? susan\u0092s gay! they\u0092re being gay together!", "answer": " emily\u0092s straight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " oh, wake up!", "answer": " wow, carol really messed you up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " yeah, she turned you into this-this-this untrusting, crazy, jealous, sycophant.  all right, so i don\u0092t know what sycophant means, but the rest is right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " look, i don\u0092t know what you\u0092re talking about, i am not a crazy, jealous person.", "answer": " huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " she\u0092s totally right! when we were together, you got all freaked out about mark and there was nothing going on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " this totally makes sense!", "answer": " it does not!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " oh, sure it does! in high school, you weren\u0092t jealous at all even though all your girlfriends were cheating on you!", "answer": " all right, all right, so up until \u009192-93 he was very trusting, then \u009294 hit, carol left him and bamn! paranoid city!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " absolutely! absolutely!", "answer": " this is so much fun!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " this is not fun!", "answer": " look, all we\u0092re trying to say is, don\u0092t let what happened with carol ruin what you got with emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " yeah. the \u009292 ross wouldn\u0092t.", "answer": " well, i still think i was right about that whole mark thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " drum roll.", "answer": "  okay. okay. all right. help! am i a mark, or a john?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " nah, you\u0092re not tall enough to be a mark, but you might make a good barney.", "answer": " all right look, am i serious, okay? tomorrow at 3:30 i am going down to the courthouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " you\u0092re actually going through with this?", "answer": " hey, look, this name has been holding me back my entire life. okay, it\u0092s probably why kids picked on me in school, and why i never do well with women\u009a so, as of 4 o\u0092clock tomorrow, i\u0092m either gonna be mark johnson or john markson.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " you got problems because of you! not your name! all right, this has got to stop! chandler is a great name! in fact\u0097yes,  i\u0092m, i\u0092m sorry. i know you really wanted me to name the baby joey, but eh, so, i\u0092m-i\u0092m, i\u0092m gonna, i\u0092m gonna name the baby chandler.", "answer": "  really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " yeah, but you have to keep the name too!", "answer": " okay. thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " you wanna hug it out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yay!", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " yay\u0097oh\u0097yay! okay, i gotta go tell frank and alice! right now!", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " bye, pheebs!", "answer": " okay, bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " ha! ha! ha!", "answer": " ohh!  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " nice luggage.", "answer": " i was gonna say\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey! i missed you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " oh, i missed you too.", "answer": "  thanks for everything, i had such a great time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep18.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}]